# **Debjeet Banerjee**

# 38, Path Bari Lane, Panihati, Sodepur, Kol-114 (+91) 91639 80758

whokilleddb@protonmail.com

Github (1) LinkedIn (1) Twitter

Cyber Security professional with 2+ years of experience. Skilled in web application penetration testing, application security, binary exploitation, and network penetration testing. Currently focused on securing Open Source Software, while pursuing *my Bachelor's in Technology (CS).* 

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**PAYATU** Pune, India

Security Consultant Intern

February 2022–Present

- Perform comprehensive web application and network penetration tests for clients along with comprehensive reporting on the same
- Design challenges for Capture the Flag events
- Write educational blogs on various security related topics

#### CYBERPWN TECHNOLOGIES

BANGALORE, INDIA

Security Analyst Intern

Nov 2021-Jan 2022

- Carry out penetration testing activities across client web applications and networks to identify vulnerabilities and bugs in the application.
- Perform configuration reviews and static code analysis
- Develop automation scripts to enhance offensive security capabilities and provide hands-on training to development teams on secure code practices

**CYBERFRAT** MUMBAI, INDIA

Technical Project Intern

June 2021-August 2021

- Design enterprise security posture and architecture
- Set up proper access management integration
- Setup endpoint management systems like UEM, EMM and MDM
- Compare services across various vendors to bring forth the most optimal solutions for clients

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Junior Penetration Tester | eLearnSecurity
- CNSS Certified Network Security Specialist | ICSI
- Splunk 7.x Fundamentals Part -1
- **Splunk User Behavior Analytics**
- **Network Protocols and Architecture | CISCO**
- Introduction to Cybersecurity | NYU

## **PUBLISHED CVE(s)**

- <u>CVE-2022-0845</u>: Code Injection in GitHub repository pytorchlightning/pytorch-lightning prior to 1.6.0.
- CVE-2021-42192: Konga v0.14.9 is affected by a privilege escalation vulnerability.
- CVE-2022-2054: Command Injection in GitHub repository nuitka/nuitka prior to 0.9.

### **PROJECTS**

- <u>1s0lat3</u>: A Linux sandbox written from scratch using **C** which uses **Namespaces** to create a docker-like containerised environment.
- Follina: A PoC Exploit for CVE-2022-30190: "Follina"
- Smoochum: A LD\_PRELOAD based rootkit inspired directly by the infamous Jynx Rootkit
- Fake Stream: Use v4l2loopback kernel modules and ffmpeg to create a shell script which takes a video as input and streams it on loop as your webcam output.
- <u>LazarusOS</u>: A **Rust-based** operating system written entirely from scratch.
- <u>Weaponizing OpenWRT</u>: Turn a **TP-MR3020** Router into a Linux computer with networking tools cross compiled for **MIPS** architecture.
- Multiple Exploits for popular 0-day and N-Day Vulnerabilities

## **MENTORING/VOLUNTEERING**

- Security Researcher at IEM IEDC
- Cyber Security chapter lead with GDSC, CC, ACM
- Winter of Code Mentor 2020
- Mentor with Smile India Foundation

### OTHER FOSS CONTRIBUTIONS

- Contributed to security tools like Metasploit and Social Engineering Toolkit
- Contributor at OWASP Pygoat
- Fixed Security vulnerabilities in **Pytorch-lightning**
- Fix security vulnerabilities in **CommaAI**, **flairNLP**, **etc**.

## **PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES**

Python

C

Bash

ASM

• Rust

Javascript

## **EDUCATION**

## INSTITUTE OF ENGINEERING AND MANAGEMENT

Bachelor of Technology(CS),

CGPA: 9.63

#### ST XAVIER'S INSTITUTION

ISC Examination,

Percentage of Marks: 97.25%